succeedwithsean.com 2015-12-21

# Succeed With Sean Mize | Take Your Internet Marketing to the Next Level » Privacy Policy

**Website Privacy Policy**

Sean Mize International, Inc  
6834 S University #429  
Centennial, CO 80122

This document governs the privacy policy of our Website, succeedwithsean.com   Any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the same meaning as where they are defined elsewhere on our Website.

**Definitions**  
“Non-Personal Information” (NPI) is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically when you access our Website with a web browser.  
“Personally Identifiable Information” (PII) is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained for us to provide you with a product or service.  PII may include information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card information, and other related information that you provide to us.

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**  
Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII.

Sean Mize International, Inc is committed to the security and privacy of all our customers.  We take your privacy seriously, and we will work with you to ensure that you have an enjoyable online experience.

Sean Mize International, Inc and our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our Website may contain links to other websites.  You understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy.  These websites will likely have their own privacy policies.  We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience.  
You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk.  It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

**Information We Collect**  
Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website.  As a visitor to our Website, you can browse our Website to find out more about us.  You are not required to provide us with any PII as a Visitor.

However, if you register as a Member to use our Website, you must provide PII in order for us to provide you with various features and/or functionality from our Website.   As a Member, we collect your PII in the following ways:

**At Member Registration**  
When you register for membership, we collect your name and email address {and other information listed}.  
**Online Forms**  
There may be online forms used in our Website.  The information you enter into these online forms may contain PII.

**Computer Information Collected**

When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website.  Such information is typically considered NPI.  We may also collect any of the following:  
**Cookies**  
Our Website uses “Cookies.” A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser.  We use Cookies to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited.  We may also use Cookies to identify you as a Member so that you can access various parts or features of our Website.  Finally, we may use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website.  Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies.  However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access features on our Website correctly or at all.  We never place PII in Cookies.  
**Web Beacons**  
We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails.  Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website.  We do not link NPI from Web Beacons to PII without your permission.  
**Automatic Information**  
We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device.  This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website.  This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system.  We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

**How Information is Used**  
We use the information we receive from you as follows:  
**Providing and Improving Our Website**  
We may use the PII you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to provide our Website to you as well as to make improvements to it.

**Communications and Email Alerts**  
When we communicate with you about our Website, we will use the email address you provided when registering as a Member.  We may also send you Website alerts regarding your use of our Website.  Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about our Website or offers from us or our affiliates, unless you have opted out of receiving such information.  You can change contact preferences at any time through your account.  While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving Website alerts.

**Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties**  
We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your PII to third parties for marketing purposes.  However, we may use your Non Personal Information for data aggregation purposes which might be sold to other parties at our discretion.  Any such data aggregation would not contain any of your PII.  We may provide your PII to affiliates that provide services with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, webhosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective Websites and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.

**Community Discussion Boards**  
Our Website may offer the capability for Users to communicate with each other through online Community Discussion Boards.  We do not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards.  If you chose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any PII as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose PII through such postings.

**Legally Required Releases of Information**  
We may be legally required to disclose your PII, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of our company, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

**Disclosures to Successors**  
If our business is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would become responsible for providing the Website to you, we retain the right to transfer your PII to the new business.  The new business would retain the right to use your PII according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business.

**Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties**  
We believe in everyone’s right to privacy.  If any postings you make to our Website contain information about third parties, you need to make sure you have permission to include them in your posting.  While we are not legally liable for the actions of our Users, we will remove any postings for which we are notified that such postings violate the privacy rights of others.

**Changing Your Information**  
You may change your PII at any time using facilities found on our Website.  If you need assistance with updating your PII or removing yourself from our mailing lists, just send us an email with your request or contact us using the Contact us information found on our Website.

**Opting Out of Sharing Information**  
You can always opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information.  Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept.

**“California Do Not Track” Settings**  
Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our Website does not track your movement within our Website.  Our Website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and detected by our Website. However, this does not change our compliance in any other way with our Privacy Policy.

**Change and Turn off tracking features in your browser** **.** You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser by visiting the following links:  
For Internet Explorer visit: http://goo.gl/0taI7I  
For Mozilla Firefox visit: http://goo.gl/IKxt9l  
For Google Chrome visit: http://goo.gl/NQIkqE  
For Safari visit: http://goo.gl/7XCOzL

Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. Google provides a free add-on to most major browsers that you can install to prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. Visit the following link to download the free Google Opt-out Add-on Tool: http://goo.gl/Ls82zv

Protecting Your Child’s Privacy  
We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).  Even though our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Website.  We do not knowingly collect PII from a child.  If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child is using our Website, please contact us.  We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information.  If we discover on our own that a child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties.  You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so.  If you are a child, please seek the permission of a parent or guardian before accessing our Website.

**Our Email Policy**  
We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act.  You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or our affiliates.  We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business.

**Use of Credit Cards**  
You may have to provide a credit card to buy products and services from our Website.  We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services.  We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use.  However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
As necessary to address changes in laws or our business practices, we may modify our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to address these changes.  Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective when published and replace any prior Privacy Policies.  We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to make sure you still agree with it.
